Hello, Yuna-chan.
こんにちは、ユナちゃん
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛いね
Isn't it said often?
よく言われるでしょ?
Will it be said?
言 われる?
sometimes.
たまに
My skin is pure white.
肌真っ白で
You're nervous.
緊張してるね
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
What do you usually play?
普段何して遊んでるの?
I'm playing games.
ゲームして遊んでます
game?
ゲーム?
What game is this?
何のゲームやの?
Apex The one from Apex's meeting?
Apex Apexさんの打ち合いのやつ?
Can you do it?
でき るの?
Is it difficult?
難しいやつ?
can.
できます
That's amazing, see you then.
すごいんだね、じゃあね
You look really young though.
すごい幼そうに見えるけどさ
Have you ever had a boyfriend?
彼氏とかいたことある?
Only one person.
一人だけ
Only one person?
一人だけ?
yes.
はい
There's only one person so far.
今まで一人だけなんだ
yes.
はい
How old are you now?
今何歳?
I'm 18 now.
今18です
I've only had one in 18 years.
18年間で一人だけなんだ
Do you have more experience?
経験人数はもっと多いでしょ?
No, just one person.
いや、一人だけ
Only one person has experience.
経験人数も一人なんだ
It's super hot and expensive.
超気象化し高いじゃん
That's amazing.
すごいね
Then I'll be nervous.
じゃあ緊張しちゃうね
There are only perverts, but is it okay?
変態しかいないけど大丈夫?
yes.
はい
That's right.
だよね
What do you think you're doing now?
今何してる気がする?
What do you like?
何が好きなの?
It's been hot lately, so I'm looking forward to going out to find shaved ice.
最近 暑いんで、かき氷を探しに行くっていうのが楽しみです
There are a lot of things like high quality shaved ice.
高級かき氷みたいなのいっぱいあるもんね
That's right.
そうなんですよ
That's what I like.
そういうの好きなんだ
Don't you like ordinary sweets?
普通のスイーツは好きじゃないの?
I like it.
好きです
Do you like that too?
それも好き?
That's right.
そうなんだ
I see.
なるほどね
When I asked you a quick glance earlier,
さっきちょっとチラッと聞いたら、
Is it true that it was done nearby?
近いでやってたって本当?
That's amazing.
すごいね
I did it quite a bit.
結構やってたんだ
About 2 years.
2年くらい
I did it for about two years.
2年くらいやってたんだ
That's serious.
ガチやん
That's amazing.
すごいな
Well then, show me your pretty face.
じゃあそのさ、きれいな顔ちょっと見せてみてよ
Take off your mask.
マスクとって
cute.
かわいい
Hey, look this way.
ほら、こっち向いて
Your face is so cute.
すんごいかわいいじゃん、顔
It looks like a kitten.
子猫みたいだね
kitten?
子猫?
Do you have a cute face like a kitten?
子猫みたいなかわいい顔してる?
Men are popular, aren't they?
モテるでしょ、男の人が
I'm not popular.
モテないです
Is that so?
そうなの?
Are you not really interested?
あんま興味ないの?
To a man.
男の人に
Okay.
よっ
Did it come out?
出てきた?
Finally.
ようやく
yes.
はい
I'm interested.
興味が
What kind of man do you like?
どういう男の人が好きだ?
I like interesting people.
面白い人が好きです
Interesting person?
面白い人?
So you're like a comedian?
じゃあ芸人みたいなってこと?
I won't go as far as being a comedian though.
芸人までは行かないけど
Are you a cool and interesting person?
かっこよくて面白い人ってこと?
that's right.
そうです
Ah, you don't have to have a good face.
あ、顔が良くないっていけないんだ
That's not the case though.
そんなことはないですけど
Looks like it's worn out.
ボロ出しちゃったみたいな
I see, somewhere.
そっか、どっか
I see.
なるほどね
Well then, Yuuna-chan, why don't you stand up?
じゃあちょっとさ、ゆうなちゃん立ってみ?
Certainly, there are idols like this.
確かに、こういうアイドルいるわ
How many centimeters tall?
身長何センチ?
It is 158.
158です
It looks even smaller.
もっとちっちゃく見えるね
Facially.
顔的に
It looks about 150 cm.
150センチくらい見える
The face.
顔は
What about your face?
顔は?
Yeah.
うん
How many cup breasts?
おっぱい何カップ?
It's D.
Dです
B cup?
Bカップ?
D is better than C.
CよりのDです
I have a D cup.
Dカップあるんだ
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみですね
Why did you find out?
なんでバレてんの?
I'm embarrassed.
恥ずかしくて
I see.
そっか
Now, look back a little.
じゃあちょっと後ろ向いてみて
This is JK, completely.
これJKだね、完全に
Just roll up that skirt.
そのままそれスカート巻き上げてみて
On top.
上に
Like this, yes.
こうやって、そう
The butt.
お尻の方
The butt?
お尻の方?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
yes.
はい
Look this way.
こっち向いて
As shown.
見せたまま
If there's only one person, you won't know what the butt edge is.
一人しかいないんじゃ、お尻エッジとか分かんないもんね
Because I've never been told that.
言われたことないから
yes.
はい
copper?
どう?
Is this your first time being photographed?
初めて撮られて?
How do you feel?
どんな気分?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Look over there too.
そこもこっち向いて
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Let's wet it slowly, me.
ゆっくり濡らしてみよっか、俺
Kuro-chan, look forward to it.
黒ちゃん、楽しみ
I'm looking forward to it all the time.
ずっと楽しみ
Your skin is white.
肌白いね
It's not white.
白いじゃねえ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's cute to wear underneath.
可愛い下に着てんじゃん
Be careful.
気をつけ
It's cute to wear underneath.
可愛い下に着けてるね
favorite?
お気に入り?
yes.
はい
The style is really nice.
スタイルめちゃくちゃいいね
Erotic body.
エロい体
Look behind you too.
後ろも見て
Try pushing that into your pants.
それパンツ食い込ませてみて
Looks like a tea bag.
ティーバッグみたい
Pull it even further to the limit.
もっと限界まで上に引っ張って
Erotic.
エロ
You've never been made to look like this, have you?
こんな格好させられたことないでしょ?
No.
ないです
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Try opening your legs.
足開いてみて
Have you ever been molested?
痴漢されたことあるでしょ?
No.
ないです
I'm on the bum so I'm about to get fucked.
されそうなケツしてるんだけど
Then get on all fours in front of me.
じゃあそこの四つん前になって
Take your knees there.
そこは膝かけて
that's right.
そう です
So, try sticking your butt out as hard as you can.
で、お尻思いっきりこっち突き出してみて
I was a hard worker.
苦労者やったんで
I'm a naughty girl.
エッチな子です
It seemed like I could see it a little.
ちょっと見えちゃいそうだった
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Isn't it a little damp?
ちょっと湿ってない?
Is it getting wet?
湿ってきた?
Well then, look forward this time.
じゃあ今度前向いて
Yes, just a short distance away.
はい、短い距離して
Stick your butt out as far as you can.
お尻思いっきり前に突き出して
Did you do it?
できた?
it hurts.
痛い
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃ可愛い
Erokawa.
エロカワ
Try narrowing your pants.
パンツ細めてみて
Like this.
こういう風に
Try squinting.
細めてみて
Kuru-chan, please help me with this.
くるちゃんこれ手伝ってあげて
It's too far away.
もっと遠すぎる
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It looks so cute.
すげー可愛く撮れてる
Kuru-chan.
くるちゃん
Beautiful.
綺麗な
Would you like to see my white breasts?
白いおっぱい見ちゃおうか
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
beautiful.
綺麗
Look this way.
こっち向いて
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗じゃん
nice.
いいね
Just up.
ちょうどアップ
why.
なんで
It's too embarrassing.
恥ずかしすぎる
A-chan.
あちゃん
Down
下
too.
も
You're doing it so smoothly.
ス ルスルにしてるんだね
Just sit there.
そこ座ってごらん
Boredom is good.
退屈がいい
Try opening it slowly.
ゆっくり開いてみして
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
Please come earlier.
もっと前に来てごらん
Earlier.
もっと前
Open your legs more.
足もっと開いて
It's so naughty.
すごいエッチじゃん
This is embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね、これ
It's super naughty.
超エッチだよ
Please open it slowly yourself.
ゆっくり自分で開いてごらん
Do it with your hands, from the side.
手やって、横から
Everything is the same all the way to the back.
奥まで全部一緒
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
Kuru-chan, I'll open your hands even more.
くるちゃん、手だってもっと開いてあげる
Like this hole below.
下のこの穴とか
You can see all the way to the hole.
穴まで丸見え
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Only one person has ever been inside, right?
一人しか入ったことないんでしょ、
this.
これ
In a very erotic way
すごいエロい形して
Ru.
る
Next time, good luck.
今 度よ、つんばいな
Just now, I started to feel stiff.
さっきのとこ、しりつきだした
oh yeah.
そうそう
Kuru-chan, don't even spread your hands.
くるちゃん、手だって広げなき
Yeah.
ゃ
Try doing it yourself.
自 分で手でやってごらん
Open your butt hole.
お尻の穴開いてごらん
Maybe I should go earlier.
もっと前に行ったほうがいいかな
It's better to lose your balance.
バランス崩すの行ったほうがいい
With both hands.
両手で
Yes, with both hands.
そう、両手で
Very erotic.
めっちゃエロい
I'm taking it all down to the butt.
お尻まで全部取ってるよ
Just like that.
そのまま
Do your best to open it.
頑張って開いてみて
cute face
かわいい顔
Try opening it again.
もう一気に開いてみて
Well, let's try again.
じゃあ、もう一回しよう
Was it embarrassing?
恥ずかしかった?
I took it to the deepest hole.
一番奥の穴のところまで取ってる
Sumizu.
すみず
It was taken away.
取られちゃったね
Kuru-chan, look at this cute face.
くるちゃん、このかわいい顔見て
Can you come closer?
近寄ってみ?
It's cute.
かわいいね
Look at Kuru-chan's face.
くるちゃんの顔見て
Chew it.
チューしてごらん
Don't let go.
離しちゃダメ
Look here.
こっち見て
こっち見てごらん
So, I'm going to let out my tongue.
で、ベロ出しちゃう
And what about Kuru-chan?
で、くるちゃん、なんて
This Kururu-chan is going to let out her tongue.
このくるちゃん、ベロ出しちゃう
Suck it.
吸ってごらん
Suck loudly.
音立てて吸ってごらん
Take a deep breath
いっぱい吸ってごら
yeah.
ん
This Kuru-chan will let out a lot of tongue.
この くるちゃん、ベロいっぱい出しちゃう
Lick each other's left side.
左舐め合って
While looking at me.
こっち見てながら
Look at the camera.
カメラ見て
I'm really going to let out a lot of tongue.
ほんといっぱいベロ出しちゃう
And then there's Kuru-chan.
そして次くるちゃん
Take another lick.
もう一杯舐めごらん
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Look at my face being licked.
舐められてる顔見してごらん
Do your breasts feel good?
おっぱい気持ちいい?
Look at the face being licked.
舐められてる顔見て
My boobs are sitting.
おっぱい座れてるよ
Kuru-chan, what do you think of idol breasts?
くるちゃん、アイドルのおっぱいどうよ?
Highest?
最高?
Kuru-chan, what's the opposite?
くるちゃん、反対はなんて
Just sit there.
そこ座らしちゃえ
While opening your pussy.
おまんこ開きながら
Open your legs.
足開いて
Pool boobs.
プールおっぱいな
My pussy is so pink.
おまんこすごいピンクになってる
Kuru-chan seems to be getting more tongue-tied.
くるちゃん、もっとベロベロになるみたいな
I'm being licked.
舐められてる
Look, it's being licked.
見てみ、舐められてる
Kuribinbinjan.
くりびんびんじゃん
Divided?
分かれた?
By yourself.
自分で
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
Open your pussy for yourself.
おまんこ、自分で最後開いてごらん
Open it and look this way.
開いて、こっち向いてごらん
It's standing really well.
くりすごい立ってるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
Close
く る
Chan, come here.
ちゃん、 こっち来て
Kuru-chan, sit here.
くるちゃん、ここ座って
What is this?
これ何だ?
what?
何ですか?
Chin chin.
ちんちん
Don't you know?
知ってるんじゃない?
First, stretch it out.
まず、伸ばしてごらん
Why is it moving?
何で動いてる?
It's moving.
動いてる
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Where is it suitable?
どこで向いてる?
get nervous?
緊張する?
Try touching it with your hands.
手で触ってごらん
Tsuntsun.
つんつん
Try touching the tip all the way.
先っぽいっぱい触ってごらん
Try holding it with this hand.
この手で握ってごらん
Make that dick bigger.
そのちんちん大きくして
Just stay still like that.
そうやっていじっと
So cute.
すごいかわいい
Look how big it's gotten.
でっかくなってきてごらん
Look.
見て
Just smell it.
匂い嗅いでみ
copper?
どう?
Yeah.
うん
copper?
どう?
Don't you know?
わかんない?
Was it a lie?
嘘だった?
It smells good.
いい匂いする
Guess the dick face.
ちんちん顔当ててみ
cute face
かわいい顔
You've never had a penis hit on your cheek, have you?
ほ っぺにちんちん当てられたことないでしょ?
Why not try it yourself?
自分からチューしてみ?
Give me a little tongue.
ちょっとベロ出して
I want to lick the tip.
先っぽちろちろ舐めたいな
Slower.
もっとゆっくり
Give me more tongue.
もっとベロ出して
too
も
You have to lick the whole thing, right?
っと 全体舐めなきゃダメでしょ?
If you lick the entire tip.
先っぽ全部舐めたら
All the potash parts.
カリの部分全部
Blue on the back.
裏の青
OK?
Add that.
それ加えてみ
Roll.
巻く
Still, I'll leave it there to make you feel better.
それでも置いて気持ちよくしてあげる
It's full in your mouth.
口の中いっぱいだね
Lick it deeper.
もっと奥で舐めて
Make more noise.
もっと音立てて
A very naughty sound.
すごいエッチな音が
I'm letting a lot fall.
ほんといっぱい落ちさせてる
Then take that out.
じゃあそれ抜いて
Look at the bullet.
弾舐めてごらん
I'll lick more.
もっと舐めます
Lick it all.
全部舐めて
Also the opposite.
反対もね
Hold the penis in your hand as well.
ちんちん反対も手で持って
That's one more time.
それもう一回
Put it in your mouth.
口の中入れてみ
It's tongue all the way to the top.
上までベロってなって
Down.
下
Looks like it's ahead.
先っぽいね
It became more disgusting.
もっと嫌らしくなって
Give me a lot of tongue.
ベロいっぱい出して
Just react.
そのまま反応して
Faster.
もっと早く
Go around faster.
もっと早く回って
Please talk a lot.
いっぱい喋ってください
Please make yourself comfortable.
気持ちよくしてください
Is dick delicious?
ちんちんおいしい?
Please sit on the sofa.
ソファー座ってごらん
Get on your feet.
足上に乗って
Get on top.
上に乗って
Try talking.
喋ってごらん
Kuro-chan, please move.
黒ちゃん動いてごらん
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
You can't just quit Kuro-chan.
そのまま黒ちゃんやめちゃダメ
My legs are contradictory.
足矛盾して
While showing it unconsciously.
思わなく見せながら
Hands get in the way.
手邪魔
Hand it off.
手どけて
Your mouth is full of dick.
お口の中、ちんちんいっぱいだね
Pull it out once and see how big your hair is.
一回抜いて、どんだけ大きい髪して
When it was bigger than Yuna-chan's face.
ゆうなちゃんの顔より大きい頃
beside.
横
Kuro-chan's time too.
黒 ちゃんもタイム
happy?
うれしい?
Mix it up with your hands.
手でこんでいじって
Try licking it while you play with it.
手いじりながら先、ペロペロしてごらん
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Please make me feel good.
いっぱい気持ちよくしてあげてください
Add your signature.
サイン加えて
Add one.
一本加えて
Hands get in the way.
手邪魔
Kuro-chan, here.
黒ちゃん、ここに
painful?
苦しい?
Are you going to bully Yuuna-chan next time?
今度、ゆうなちゃんいじめよっか
Come to bed.
ベッドおいで
Look here.
こっち見て
It's seriously cute.
マジで可愛いやん
Kuro-chan is lying down.
黒ちゃん横着
You can't hide it after all.
やっぱ隠しちゃダメ
Try talking.
喋ってごらん
child
こ
Tchi.
っち
Make your face cute.
可愛 い顔にして
While having breasts.
おっぱいながらて
Black-chan is safe.
黒ちゃん安全
Go on and on.
どんどんしていってごらん
Here.
こ っち
Chew your whole body.
全身チューして
Make that one book.
それ一本にして
Open it.
開いて
Open your legs more.
もっと足開いて
licking.
ペロペロ
Make it a face.
顔にして
Kuro-chan, open up.
黒ちゃん開いて
Chew.
チューして
There are so many more chestnuts.
くりもっといっぱいなんて
Everything from the bottom.
下から全部
Try breathing it naturally.
くりとる自然に吸ってみ
In your mouth.
口の中に
Kuro-chan.
黒ちゃん
Insert the entire bottom into the hole.
穴に下全部入れて
Do you know what's in there?
入ってるのわかる?
Kuro-chan, calm down more.
黒ちゃん、もっと落ち立つ
Suck it.
吸っては
yes.
そう
Kuro-chan, calm down more.
黒ちゃん、もっと落ち立つ
I smoked it.
吸ったの
Where are you being licked?
どこ舐められてんの?
Kuro-chan, let it suck naturally.
黒 ちゃん、くりとる自然に吸ってもらおう
It's cute.
可愛いね
Let it breathe naturally.
くり立つ自然に吸ってもらおう
Look.
ほ ら
It's standing really well.
すんごい立ってるよ
Sungo
すんご
I'm standing.
い 立ってるよ
What a great bastard.
すんごい野郎よ
Can I have my secret partner suck me?
秘密の相手に吸ってもらっていい?
I understand that.
それわかる
What is it?
なんでしょうか?
I don't know.
わかんない
Do you want to stand up?
く り 立 つかい?
You like chestnuts, right?
くり好きでしょ?
Are you watching?
見してる?
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Are you doing this?
こうしてる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
See more.
もっといっぱい見して
Kuro-chan is talking.
黒ちゃん、喋ってるし
So different.
すんごい違う
Want to try it yourself?
自分でやってみる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいとか?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Did I mention it felt good?
気持ちいいの言ったのし?
So different.
すんごい違う
Sungo
す ん ご
No. No.
い 違う
Kuro-chan is talking.
黒 ちゃん、喋ってるよ
Did I say okay?
いいの言ったの?
Good.
よいしょ
Okay.
よ いしょ
Did I mention it felt good?
気持ちいいの言ったのし?
So different.
すんごい違う
Did I mention it felt good?
気持ちいいの言ったのし?
Did you feel good?
気 持 ち よ かった?
Can I use one more?
もっと1つ使っていい?
Good.
よいしょ
No way.
やだ
use?
使う?
Are you in such a futto?
こんなふっとに入ってんの?
copper?
どう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Do you see something stirring?
なんかかき回されてるのわかる?
Did you just come in like this?
こんなふっとに入っちゃったの?
I don't understand this though.
これわかんないけど
I don't understand this.
これわかんない
It ended with a transformation.
変身で終わった
This is Waka
これ わか
No.
ん ない
So different.
すんごい違う
Come in.
入 って
Come in and show me your face.
入って顔を見せて
I have become a Yotsunba.
よつんばになってきた
Yotsuda.
よつんだ
I noticed it behind me.
後ろに気づいた
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I went all the way in.
奥まで入っちゃった
Let me see it
見てさせてもらって
good?
いい?
It got really good.
すごい うまくなった
Face here.
顔こっちに
I'm lying down.
横になってる
To the side.
横に
Legs on this side.
足こっちの方
You'll understand even if you go deep inside.
奥まで入ってもわかるでしょ
It fell off a bit.
ちょっと落ちた
How many pieces did I need?
何個かっていくらいいった
Which one?
どっちの?
Kuru-chan, such a finger.
くるちゃん、そんな指
Hand-cranked.
手回し
Does it feel good on top?
上の気持ちいい?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's very tidy.
すんごいしまってる
Please show me a lot.
いっぱい見せてごらん
Spin inside.
中でぐりぐりして
refer to.
指
I wrote a lot.
いっぱい書きました
Open your fingers and show me.
指開いて見せて
Kuru-chan there.
そこでくるちゃん
That's amazing.
すごいやろ
Finally, pull out your finger and show me.
最後、指抜いて見せて
What are you doing with your pussy?
おまんこ何にして
Open deep inside the line.
線の奥まで開いて
Kuru-chan, you got licked.
くるちゃん、舐められたでしょ
I agree.
そうだね
Isn't it like this?
こうでしょ
Next time, throw it to Yuna-chan.
今度、ゆなちゃん投げて
I hope you feel comfortable just now.
さっきのとき気持ちよくしてごらん
Drop more.
もっと落として
Bring out the bell.
ベルを出して
From below.
下から
Just give it all up.
仮まで全部投げて
towards the front.
表の方に
Try using your hands too.
手も使ってごらん
One hand happens to be even more.
片手、たまたまさらに
There are also things.
もんもある
Go deep inside.
奥までくらって
Hold it and stop.
くらえてストップして
Look at Kuru-chan like this.
こういうくるちゃん見えて
I have a lot to do, so I'm going to have it at home.
いっぱいするんで、うちにうちに
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
Might be sucking.
しゃぶっているかもしれない
Kuru-chan, please be patient.
くるちゃんも耐えて
Kuru-chan is also at my house.
うちにもくるちゃんも
Me too.
私もです
This self.
この自分
quickly.
早く
Good.
よいしょ
Show me one day.
一日見せて
It's really big.
すごく大きいね
Yuno-chan also throws her pussy.
ゆうのちゃんもまんこ投げて
I can't do whitewash.
しっくせないし
Kuru-chan also put his hands on it.
くるちゃんも手を入
It is.
れて
Wow big.
すごい 大きい
feeling
気 持 ち
Please take care.
よ くしてごらん
Make yourself comfortable.
気 持ちよくしてごらん
Without this hand.
この手なしで
The biggest.
一番大きい
Kuru-chan is there.
くるちゃん、そこにいる
Let me push you more.
もっと押させて
Bring this on.
こいつもたらして
Put that dick in there.
そのチンチン入れてごらん
This one too.
こっちも
Insert your own dick too.
自分のチンチンも入れて
I was so surprised.
そんなにびっくり
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいね
Show me more.
もっと見せて
Kuru-chan.
く る ちゃん
Feel good.
気持ちよく
Try throwing more.
もっといっぱい投げてごらん
Ching Chin.
チンチン
It's really big.
すごく大きいね
Try throwing it yourself.
自分で投げてごらん
Try doing it next time using the letter M.
今度M字でやってごらん
Can you do that?
それできる?
Lift your butt up by yourself.
自分でお尻を浮かして
Come in.
入ってごらん
Get your hands behind me.
後ろに手ついて
earlier.
さっきの
Kuru-chan.
くるちゃん
It's all in there and I'm running away.
全部入ってて逃げるよ
Look.
ほ ら
Wake up!
起きてごらん
Better sit down.
座ったほうが
Make sure it's included.
入っているようにして
Kuru-chan, stop.
くるちゃん、ストップ
Try throwing it yourself.
自分で投げてごらん
It will make you feel really good.
チンチン気持ちよくしてもらえちゃう
My nose opens.
鼻開いちゃう
A very simple nose.
すごくシンプルな鼻
Below, Kuru-chan, it looks like teeth.
下、くるちゃん、歯みたいな
Please make me feel comfortable here.
こっちに気持ちよくしてごらん
Did you enter?
入 った?
It's moving.
それ動いて
Please move faster.
それもっと早く動いてごらん
This time, get on your knees.
今度、膝立てて
Hands behind you.
手、後ろについて
Hands, back.
手、後ろ
Look at it like it's stuck in there.
ぶっ刺さっているようにしてごらん
Kuru-chan, move slowly.
くるちゃん、ゆっくり動いて
Raise your lower back.
腰、浮かしてもらう
Put your hands behind your back.
後ろに手、ついて
Stay strong.
しっかりして
Kuru-chan, please slow down.
くるちゃん、ゆっくり早くして
Do it faster and faster.
どんどん早くして
Raise your hips more.
腰、もっと浮かして
Keep it floating.
浮かしたまま、キープ
It's no good, just do it.
ダメじゃん、勝手に
I have to tell you to go slowly.
ゆっくり行くのって言わないと
Hey, more yourself.
ほら、もっと自分で
Raise your hips.
腰、浮かして
Just keep it.
そのまま、キープ
Kuru-chan from below.
くるちゃん、下から
Move quickly.
早く動いて
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
Don't twirl around anymore.
もう、くるくるしてないで
Well then, let's move forward.
じゃあ、前を出す
Become here if you fall.
ここに落ちる場合になって
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Chinchin, I don't know if it's coming out.
ちんちん、出られてるか分からない
I went again.
また、行っちゃったの
It's already 1km deep.
もう、1キロ奥まで
Have you lost your strength?
力抜けちゃった?
I've been there a lot.
いっぱい行っちゃったもんな
Look this way.
こっち向いて
I went again.
また、行っちゃった
Against normal.
正常に対する
Kuru-chan,
くるちゃん、
Once next to me.
一 回横で
Like the hassle from earlier.
さっきの手間みたいに
yes.
そう
Look carefully.
よく見て
Don't hide it well.
しっくり隠すな
About the most.
一番くらいついて
A lot of juice comes out of my pussy.
おまんこの汁いっぱい出る
Make your pussy feel good.
おまんこ、気持ちよくして
Kuru-chan.
く る ちゃん
Look this way.
こっち向いて
I have to go further.
もっと、ゆくゆくいかないと
Kuru-chan, let it out as hard as you can.
くるちゃん、思いっきりながら出して
Look at that amazing face behind me.
すごい色い顔、後ろにほら
Kuru-chan, let it all out.
くるちゃん、全部出して
A lot came out.
すごいいっぱい出たよ
Finally, clean this up.
最後、これきれいにして
Clean it to the deepest part.
一番奥まできれいにして
From below.
下から
Clean everything.
全部きれいにして
Finally, suck it as hard as you can.
最後、思いっきりしゃぼって
Kuru-chan, it's on my mind.
くるちゃん、頭にあって
Was it clean?
きれいにできた?
Did you do it?
できた?
It was so cute.
めっちゃかわいかったね
What do you think?
どうだって?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
See you next time.
またさ、今度会おうよ
Hiwari did it.
ひわりやった